{
    "name": ".\\GoogleACE\\Create and Manage Cloud Resources\\CreateHttpLoadBalancer.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute firewall-rules create fw-allow-health-check --network=default --action=allow --direction=ingress --source-ranges=130.211.0.0/22,35.191.0.0/16 --target-tags=allow-health-check --rules tcp:80",
                "gcloud compute firewall-rules create fw-allow-health-check --network=default --action=allow --direction=ingress --source-ranges=130.211.0.0/22,35.191.0.0/16 --target-tags=allow-health-check --rules=tcp:80"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute firewall-rules create fw-allow-health-check --network=default --action=allow --direction=ingress --source-ranges=130.211.0.0/22, 35.191.0.0/16 --target-tags=allow-health-check --rules=tcp:80",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1705339244.5648444,
            "question": "How would you create a health check firewall rule called fw-allow-health-check with target tags 'allow-health-check' that allows TCP traffic on port 80?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute health-checks create http http-basic-check --port 80",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1705338575.1530423,
            "question": "How would you create a health check called http-basic-check on port 80 for a load balancer?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute addresses describe lb-ipv4-l --format=\"get(address)\" --global"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute addresses describe lb-ipv4-1 --format=\"get(address)\" --global",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1705339060.8937576,
            "question": "How would you view the info of an IP address object called lb-ipv4-1?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute backend-services create web-backend-service --protocol=HTTP --port-name=HTTP --health-checks=http-basic-check --global",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1705339411.5709321,
            "question": "How would you create a backend service called web-backend-service that uses HTTP and health-check 'http-basic-check'?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "1. Create load balancer template 2. Create managed instance group 3. Create health check firewall rule 4. Create static global IP 5. Create load balancer health check 6. Create backend service 7. Add service group to backend service 8. Create URL map 9. Create target HTTP proxy 10. Create global forwarding rule",
                "1. Create load balancer template 2. Create managed instance group 3. Create health-check firewall rule 4. Create global static IP 5. Create health-check for load balancer 6. Create backend service 7. Add instances to backend 8. Create URL map 9. Create target HTTP proxy 10. Create global forwarding rule",
                "1. Create load balancer template 2. Create managed instance group 3. Create health-check firewall rule 4. Create global static IP 5. Create health-check for load balancer 6. Create backend service 7. Add instances to backend 8. Create URL map 9. Create HTTP target proxy 10. Create global forwarding rule"
            ],
            "answer": "1. Create load balancer template 2. Create managed instance group 3. Create health-check firewall rule 4. Set global static external IP address 5. Create health-check for load-balancer 6. Create backend service 7. Add instance group to the backend service 8. Create URL map 9. Create target HTTP rpoxy 10. Create global forwarding rule",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1705338736.797944,
            "question": "What are the steps to create an HTTP load balancer?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute instance-groups managed create lb-backend-group --template=lb-backend-template --zone=us-east1-c --size=2",
                "gcloud compute instance-groups managed create lb-backend-group --size=2 --template=lb-backend-template --zone=us-east1-c"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute instance-groups managed create lb-backend-group --template=lb-backend-template --size=2 --zone=us-east1-c",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705337992.1358595,
            "question": "How would you create a Managed Instance Group of 2 Vms called lb-backend-group based on a load balancer template called lb-backend-template in zone us-east1-c?",
            "tried": 2
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute url-maps create web-map-http --default-service=web-backend-service"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute url-maps create web-map-http --default-service web-backend-service",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1705338758.9036262,
            "question": "How would you create a URL map 'web-map-http' to route the incoming requests to the default backend service 'web-backend-service'?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute http-target-proxies create http-lb-proxy --url-map=web-map-http",
                "gcloud compute target-http-proxies create http-lb-proxy --url-map=web-map-http"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute target-http-proxies create http-lb-proxy --url-map web-map-http",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1705339273.8184526,
            "question": "How would you create a target HTTP proxy 'http-lb-proxy' to route requests to a URL map 'web-map-http'?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute addresses create lb-ipv4-1 --ip-version=IPV4 --global",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1705340301.800074,
            "question": "How would you set up a global static exteral IP address called lb-ipv4-1 on IPv4?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "gcloud compute forwarding-rules create http-content-rule --target-http-proxy=http-lb-proxy --address=lb-ipv4-1 --ports 80 --global",
                "gcloud compute forwarding-rules create http-content-rule --address=lb-ipv4-1 --target-http-proxy=http-lb-proxy --ports 80 --global",
                "gcloud compute forwarding-rules create http-content-rule --address=lb-ipv4-1 --target-http-proxy=http-lb-proxy --ports=80 --global"
            ],
            "answer": "gcloud compute forwarding-rules create http-content-rule --address=lb-ipv4-1 --global --target-http-proxy=http-lb-proxy --ports=80",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1705340240.0192225,
            "question": "How would you create a global forwarding rule 'http-content-rule' to route incoming requests to the proxy 'http-lb-proxy' using IP address 'lb-ipv4-1' on port 80?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gcloud compute backend-services add-backend web-backend-service --instance-group=lb-backend-group --instance-group-zone=us-east1-c --global",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1705340168.9769952,
            "question": "How would you add an instance group 'lb-backend-group' as a backend to the backend service 'web-backend' in zone us-east1-c?",
            "tried": 2
        }
    ]
}